realcouples.co.uk 2006-06-15

# Privacy policy

Privacy Policy Statement

This Privacy Policy Statement sets forth the policies and practices with respect to information or data gathered regarding paying and non-paying members of this Site. This is an adult Site that expressly and strictly limits its membership to adults. All persons under the age of majority in their jurisdiction are strictly prohibited from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site.

This Site does not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons under the age of majority.

Notice - Use of website by the paying or non-paying member constitutes the paying or non-paying member's express consent to the Use of Personal Information Collected by Site.

CAREFULLY READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT. BY YOUR USE OF THIS SITE YOU WILL BE EXPRESSLY SIGNIFYING THAT YOU AGREE TO THIS POLICY STATEMENT AND THAT YOU ASSENT TO THE USE OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU SUPPLY OR THAT IS COLLECTED ABOUT YOU AS DETAILED IN THIS POLICY STATEMENT.

IF YOU DO NOT EXPRESSLY AGREE WITH ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT YOU SHOULD NOT JOIN OR USE THIS SITE.

**Terms and Conditions of Membership**  
By accepting membership to this Site you are unconditionally accepting all of those terms and conditions. Some of those terms and conditions may also affect the right of this Site to use information that it has gathered from paying or non-paying members.

In the event of any conflicts between the Membership Terms, the Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy Statement, the provisions of this Privacy Policy shall prevail.

When any adult consumer signs on as a paying member of this site, that consumer may be required to provide certain personal as well as demographic information which may include, but is not necessarily limited to, the paying or non-paying member's name, address, birthday, e-mail address, username and password, and special interests or affiliations. This Site collects any and all such information and includes it in its customer database.

If a paying or non-paying member sends any personal communication or correspondence, by any means, to the Site, or any of its employees, agents or representatives, the Site may collect any information regarding that communication and include that information in its customer database.

**  
Chargebacks and refunds**

Our subscription fees are nonrefundable unless you contact us first. You will receive the full benefits of your membership because your password remains active until the end of the most recent paid billing period no matter when you cancel during that period.

IF YOU TRY TO DISPUTE OR DENY A VALID CHARGE, your credit card details along with your email address, name and address will immediately be added to a negative database. This negative database is shared by thousands of merchants on the Internet, both large and small, to minimise further fraud.

You will not be able to use your credit card to purchase goods or services from any of these merchants in the future. IF YOU TRY TO DISPUTE OR DENY A VALID CHARGE, you will be sent an invoice for the disputed amount by regular postal mail.

Copies will also be sent to your bank and credit card company. This invoice will include the following information:

* The name of the site you paid to access  
* Your IP address at the time you signed up  
* The date and time of your signup  
* The original charge plus a $35.00 dispute processing fee.

If you do not pay this invoice within 30 days, a second invoice will be sent. This invoice will also include the following information:

* Access logs detailing when you accessed the site in question  
* The IP Address(es) you used to access the site, and which ISP you used  
* Examples of any files, images, or other information or material protected by copyright you downloaded from the site after gaining your username and password

If the second invoice is not paid within 30 days, the charge(s) will be forwarded to one of the 17 debt collection agencies which we work with in all five continents.   
Your credit rating may be affected and you will be liable for any excess handling fees.

To avoid any of the outcomes above, we encourage you to contact us first for any problems with your purchase or subscription. We have an excellent track record in resolving problems to ensure that you are fully satisfied with your purchase. Most complaints and/or disputes are easily resolved to the satisfaction of both parties.

Our support center is located [HERE](http://support.realsexcash.com/)

S-Four Corporation  
Unit 110 Alpha Bldg. Subic International Hotel  
Rizal cor. Sta. Rita Road, Subic Bay Freeport Zone  
Olongapo City Philippines 2200
